perfectgonzo.com 2013-12-23

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy is Important to us !**

This policy explains the privacy practices of AXS Charge Ltd. ("the company" or "We"). In order to provide customer service, payment processing, billing, fraud detection and a more personalized and positive costumer experience, the company collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you'll interact with the company in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use. Your privacy is respected by us by discreetly charging your card so that there is no connection to adult products and/or service. 

**Information that is Collected**

> **Required Information**  
>  To subscribe to this service, you must voluntarily submit you full name, street address, postal code, city, state, country, email address  and you agree to be bound by the terms of service. Name and address (Zip code) information is necessary for us to protect you against credit card fraud, _nothing will ever be mailed to you_! A 128bit SSL secure transmission is used to send such information.
> 
> **Automatically retrieved information  
>  **We automatically retrieve your numberic IP address assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider as well as your browser.  
>  We also keep track of all email communication and we identify the origination IP. The access patterns of your account are also automatically logged for fraud prevention.

> **Third-Party Information**  
>  During the processing of transactions, we may collect verification information from our credit card authorization service. Our credit card authorization service verifies that users' credit card information and address matches the information that the user supplies to this site.
> 
> **Aggregate Statistical Information**  
>  We may collect aggregated statistical information for purposes of improving our service. This data does not contain personally identifying information, such as name or email address.
> 
> **Transaction Information Security**  
>  Cardholder Account and Transaction information is protected from unauthorised access by physical, electronic and procedural security measures recommended by Visa International & Mastercard International Account Information Security Best Practices Guide.

**Our Use of Information**

> **Internal Uses**  
>  We use data collected on our website in order to 1) provide our service, 2) provide customer service, and 3) improve our product. We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees/third parties who require it to fulfill customer service requests. 

> **Contacting Visitors**  
>  We may contact you about our products, sales, third party offers or conduct additional surveys with your right to opt out.
> 
> **Disclosure to Third Parties**  
>  We will not give third parties individually identifiable information about users except for the limited purposes described below.  
>  \- Whenever it is necessary to comply with the law or legal process, or to ensure the integrity and operation of our business and systems.  
>  \- When it is necessary to collect debt and pursue chargeback retrivals.  
>  \- We are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority.  
>  \- We are required to disclose it in order to process transactions.   
>  \- To fullfill customer service requirements.
> 
> **Internet Information**  
>  We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may also use IP information to reduce credit card and bank account fraud.
> 
> **Use of Cookies**  
>  We use cookies to easy the join process for uses. These cookies allow us to remember a user who visits multiple pages in our site, so that the user doesn't need to re-enter information multiple times. In addition, we use cookies to process our affiliate program; no personal information is shared with our affiliates. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 
> 
> **Notification of Changes**  
>  This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the website. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. 
> 
> **Right to Delete**  
>  You may contact us to modify or remove your account details. 

**How to Contact Us:**

> Contact AXS Charge Ltd. [here](https://secure.axscharge.com/contact.html) should you have any questions regarding this document.
